coursework.info 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy

Marked by Teachers is owned and run by The Student Room Group Ltd. 

## Introduction

Marked by Teachers is sensitive to privacy issues on the internet. We believe that it is important you know how we treat the information about you, which we receive from you. To this end we have created the following privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy on the internet and especially within the use of this website. 

## General Privacy Statement

In general you can visit Marked by Teachers without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about you. Our servers automatically collect domain names, IP addresses, browser details, your country of origin and how you got to the site (via the use of cookies and server generated technology - please see the section 'What are cookies' for more information). This information is aggregated to measure things such as the number of visits, time spent on the site, pages viewed etc. Marked by Teachers uses this information to measure the use of our site and to improve the service we offer to you. 

Personally identifiable information such as email address, home address, first and last names, and other such identifiable information is only known when voluntarily provided by a visitor for the purpose of registration. 

Personally identifiable information that is collected in response to the use of this site is retained by Marked by Teachers, and only used in the improvement of services and in contact from us, to the user. We do not sell, transfer or otherwise disclose this information outside this company, except: 

  1. where disclosure is required by law or; 
  2. when the visitor chooses to register using the online payment method (i.e. via debit or credit card). Some or all of this information is passed to our payment processor, PayPal (which ever you choose), in order for them to safely and securely process the payment information. PayPal hold and process all sensitive information securely (please contact PayPal via the contact link on their website - http://www.paypal.co.uk/uk - for information on their Privacy Statement, and security measures). 
  3. through content related and relevant email advertisements (any email advertisement is sent out by us, and none of your personally identifiable information is disclosed to the advertiser). 
  4. when you elect to submit work to our site to gain access to the database. All work that you elect to submit will be submitted, along with your name (no further information is submitted), to plagiarism detection software. The purpose of this is to protect your work against reproduction by other users. This information will not be passed further than the plagiarism detection software, and will be securely stored. 

It is your responsibility to keep your site log in information secure when it's in your possession. If you are using a shared computer, please ensure you log out of Marked by Teachers or close down the browser before leaving the computer for the next user. 

This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such Websites. 

## Email preferences

Your email address may be used to send you details of our products that we think will be useful to you. We will only send you emails in accordance with your email preferences, which you chose when you completed the registration form. 

If at any point you would like to opt-out of receiving communications from us by email, you can amend your preferences in the [My Account](http://www.markedbyteachers.com/customer/account/index/) section. 

## Third party emails

From time to time we would like to send you emails from carefully selected third parties that offer products or services that we think may be of interest to you. We will only do this if you have opted-in to receive such emails when you completed the registration form, or have since opted-in through your email preferences. 

You can amend your preferences in the [My Account](http://www.markedbyteachers.com/customer/account/index/) section. 

## What is a cookie?

The information supplied by a cookie can help us provide you with a better online experience and assist us in the profile of our visitors. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Many sites do this whenever a user visits their website in order to track online traffic flows. You have the option to set your computer to accept all cookies, to notify you when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these means that personalised services cannot be provided to that user and accordingly you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the Marked by Teachers features. For more information on cookies please visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). 

## How we use IP addresses

We may use your IP address to help diagnose any problems with our server or to administer Marked by Teachers. Your IP address may be used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information that helps us understand our users requirements. 

## Security

Marked by Teachers has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information under its control. Please try and keep your log in information (username and/or password) secure at all times. If you suspect that the security of your log in information has been breached you can gain access to your members account area and change both your password and email address under the option 'Change your E-mail address or Password'. 

## Children

Marked by Teachers is intended for general use and does not knowingly collect personal data from children. We take specific steps to protect the privacy of children by not allowing minors (users under 18 years of age) to sign up to the site unless given permission by a parent or legal guardian (please see our Terms of Service clause 8 for full details). Parents and legal guardians should supervise the online activities of their children, and should consider the use of parental control tools available from online services and software providers that help provide a child-friendly Internet environment. 

## Viewing and correcting your personal information

In the majority of cases, Marked by Teachers will allow you to view any information that is held about you if you ask for it either in an email or in writing. If you then inform us that part or all of the information is incorrect, we will review it. If we also believe that it is incorrect, we will then correct our records. 

## Third Party Advertisements

Any advertisement appearing on this website (banner and/or skyscraper) is delivered to you, on our behalf, by our web advertising partner. Information about your visit, such as the number of times you have viewed an advert (but no personally identifiable information), is used to serve the adverts. 

  1. Third party vendors, including Google, show Marked by Teachers ads on sites on the internet. 
  2. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to Marked by Teachers 
  3. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/opt-out.html). 
  4. You can opt out of the other third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and [www.struq.com/consumer-opt-out/](http://www.struq.com/consumer-opt-out/)

## Contacting Marked by Teachers

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the conduct of Marked by Teachers or your use of the service this website provides, you can contact: 

Marked by Teachers  
The Student Room Group Ltd  
The Grain Store  
127 Gloucester Road  
Brighton  
BN1 4AF 

or [Contact Us](http://www.markedbyteachers.com/contacts)
